Roxanna Shahpouri

QA TESTER/DEVELOPER

roxannashahpouri@gmail.com (407) 456-3276 Golden, CO

GitHub LinkedIn **Portfolio**

Summary

I am a junior developer with experience using JavaScript, jQuery, React, C#, Visual Studio, Unity, and Xcode. Also experienced in Data Entry and Project Management, managing remotely.

Skills

Front End: JavaScript ES6, React, jQuery, HTML5, CSS3, NPM

Back End: Node.js, PostgreSQL, RESTful APIs

Additional Tools: Git, GitHub, Slack, Bitbucket, Unity, Xcode, TestFlight

Experience

A1A SOFTWARE Fernandina Beach, FL April 2021 - Current

QA Tester/App Submission Assistant

- Testing company apps to make sure UI and Performance still meets a level of acceptance
- Doing routine QA on in-work apps and write JIRA tickets explaining issues/bugs
- Building and submitting company apps to iOS, Android, and Windows Store when needed
- Training in progress: diagnosing and fixing JIRA ticket issues

A1A SOFTWARE Fernandina Beach, FL Junior Developer July 2019 - Current

- Updating a static HTML page that maintains the list of items available to the user
- Expanding the options available to users on an ASP.NET page
- Redesigning feature pages for company products

Data Entry Manager

A1A SOFTWARE

Overseeing the daily function of the department

Delegating customer requests or issue tickets to team members

Fernandina Beach, FL January 2015 - January 2020

Recent Projects

RMNP Quiz | GitHub: A quiz app that tests the user's knowledge on Rocky Mountain National Park. Built with JavaScript, HTML5 and CSS3.

<u>Trail Finder | GitHub:</u> A search application that helps the user find trails in a specific area. Built with JavaScript, HTML5 and CSS3. Noteful | GitHub: A task management app that allows the user to create folders and notes within those folders. Built with React.

Education

THINKFUL March 2019 - November 2019

Full-Stack Web Development Program / Engineering Immersion

- Learned industry best practices and practical software development standards with a focus on HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Node.js, React, Redux, and algorithms & data structures.
- Created and deployed mobile-first applications while learning new languages and frameworks by collaborating several hours every week with a senior web developer.

VALENCIA STATE COLLEGE

Associates in Arts, Engineering

January 2010 - December 2013